I was just as lost as you
Don't flinch, I've got the scars to prove it through
A doorway cracked inside my skull at the shadow
Marching out of the dream slow quiet not giving
To shattered skies, with nothing left
But haunted highs, a thousand no's
A million tries, still Joni's name
Was in my cries
Every fall became a step I had to take
Every crack a line, I swore I'd break
They tried to dim the fire in my chest
But Johnny whispered, don't you rest
I think it's over, Jamie. I think it's over.
Thank you so much for watching this video, see you in the next one!
But who's t-
I'm in the show with Psycho Ronys.
What's up, bro?
Are you still there?
I'm good, can you hear me?
Yeah, I hear you.
How are you?
I'm good, bro.
Now you've been, I feel like I haven't talked to in years.
It's been probably like a day or two, right?
Look at that.
I'm naked right now.
I can't see you.
How are you?
I am.
Don't pull him by me yourself, bro.
Try not to.
You just saw I see myself on the TV. You have my show. You just have the show. Let's take the show
No, oh look at what cat is that?
That really
This is a cat sleeping your back. Oh, and we're good. We're here. We you can have the show. I see a little kitty
Yo, you're welcome to psyche's awakens or scolto psyche
Under the covers
My boyfriend my boyfriend's back and he's better than ever. Hey now. Hey now psyche's back. I
Was just that Alexandra mayors push she was doing a three-eyed Atlas updates. She's so funny. She thinks it's a fucking spaceship. I mean
It could
Only aliens are interested in me, not normal people, only aliens are.
Exactly.
I'm gonna be on the roof of my house with a fucking sign so you can take me.
Did I probe your butthole?
You had a what to my butthole?
I probed it.
You're not, huh?
Prove it, prove it.
I did it, I did it, I put my whole finger in it.
And then it was like, my fingers like each inch is long.
And you said more, more, more.
And I was like, oh, this guy is, he's too weird.
I put it in all the way into my fucking brain.
I put it all the way into my brain.
Just kept shoving it in my ass.
Yeah.
I gotta get something thicker, though, than the finger, bro.
We gotta find the, you know, two fingers.
I
See a little kitty cat snoring on the table by the TV
What are burning joint USA Nick Johnson my boy
Jamie's Cowboys. I think easy cameras was down there too. I saw
Not really
You're so drunk you're drunk
You bet over in the corner and I penetrated you and you said you loved it remember that I
Vaguely remember the corner. Yeah, remember
Yeah, I'm in a faint memory of it. Okay, I'm not gonna I'm not all insane
Yeah, yeah, that was my ass woke up really short of that day. I remember funny thing. Yeah, we'll give your ass
I woke up in there. It was disgusting. I can't remember nothing but my
Isn't that the thing that makes you shit with some little plastic thing you show in your ass or something you like five in a row, please
Huh
Yeah, I gotta clear my vows. I'm done. I don't know. I don't wait my man
It's good to clean the vows once in a blue little bit dirty
It was like a little bit like I look at the corner in there is like
What the hell is that thing anyway? I always saw this like a little clear little thing. What does it do? How come it makes you shit?
What's the active ingredient and that's fucking thick. It's just a saline, but they they squirt into your butthole
And so you have to like let it out. I think it will go about
I'm gonna do it too. Can I take a nice shit to a line of coke, bro? I should have made go to a bathroom
I don't would pop
Thank you come back
So what you think to your elephant is an alien spacecraft, or you think it's a bullshit
Just for about so
Do you think
Actually don't go fuck what it is
Alex what about my butter you don't feel it
I'm gonna take a fucking corona bottle and put it in there
Ron about I don't want to buy some of it. So like I see a beer bottle. I want Alexander McQueen
Esquire
You want to do you want to be? Oh, you want me?
Queen me
Yes, I want that
Um, I'm taking about it give me a second
Yeah, yeah, you could have it
Yes, okay, so imagine this
Whatever makes I grow any happier, right? Yeah, he comes to the house. He says hey, I gotta pull you over you
Go to pass here
Oh my god, someone's on the other panel the other day they were making fun of us from that video
Very much seen Alex and psyche. I think was exile talking shit
He's like that motherfucker said he wants to drag psyche by the boss into the bushes. I was dying
Well, you do and I know he's right. He's not lying, but
Reason is it was like
I can't believe you made a fucking lobster song that's hilarious
Fucking love it. That's just funny as fuck
I missed Alexander's song. I made this song for Alexander McLean.
I thought it was more of a page to fill out the song.
No, it's not for anybody else besides you because you're the first one that turns red on the beach.
Seashell spell
Alexander's preaching with a tan
So divine sunscreen
Forgotten he's turning to bright
With a lobster
People red and raw
Snapping our claws at the cosmic law
that is whispers the pot can't wait alexander rises halo of foam welcome
microstations to your new home that was all red-and-scented on the beat
with the lobster people red and raw snapping our claws at the cosmic law
Opps to people, red and raw, snapping our claws at the cosmic law, steaming our veins, salting our...
like an 80s vibe it reminds me that's a good one good job buddy
where'd everyone go why did everyone go leave here you see everyone out of the
injury again where the fuck is ghost bro
i don't know why i have permission to crash out
i'm gonna have to crash i don't actually
we have to crash out bro don't call me if we crash out
Thing that is where's that brother been haven't seen him in a few I think I've been to him like a year ago
That's impossible. He was up here all week. Oh, well, that's got him
Yeah, I feel it's a spunky nader
She's been kicked out of the show. What about
Permission to crash out
Huh?
Haha! It's the best!
Ghost already did, he took the whole town
Let it be
C'mon!
That goes through the night
That's how you know, the haunts are live
Lights flicker, chats in the ride
And somewhere goes about to die
Heroes are loud, like thunder on caffeine
Dropping stacks, cracking jokes
Keeping the scene clean
The crowd starts howling
The trolls start crying
Ghosts just grin, let's fucking
Remember, I was reborn
May I have permission to crash out?
Ghost already did it to the whole crowd
Heart of gold, voice of fire
When ghost shows up, the stakes get higher
Dum dum, that's his war
Psyche is proud
They talk so I hope why is he still around for kind
In a world full of clowns
He's the last to fake
When the screen went dark
He kept me awake
All the noise fades
But ghost remains
Turning pain into digital flame
May I have permission to crash out?
Who's pretty now?
Starry Game Cowboy
Pyschees
Amazing
Ah, it's a dream
Dong Dong
That's top 3 right there.
Is that a new version?
And that was always the same song.
Yo, yo, yo, do I have permission to crash out?
Alex wants this t-shirt gang.
It's a man to talk.
DÄ
b dom zapy.
AXXXX
All shall be revealed, that shh!
Starting!
Now the party's getting started!
There's a cooking shit about CFF, Gotti.
Whatever that is, I don't even know what CFF is.
I'm not a banger.
I'm tight.
CFF, what is that bullshit though?
It's not the first time I heard it.
Hey me girl. Hey me girl. Where's cheer your boy?
Stop playing my peeps hit that link hit that like button come support your boy psycharone's all the true supporters
Everyone wants to ride the limo, right?
When my man's in the limo and fuck it,
everyone's on his dick.
But you know, when the limo breaks down
and he's gotta take the bus,
that's when you see who your real friends are.
We'll take the bus with you.
Bunch of crazy people out there, man.
You're heard.
Stop playing with McQueen.
Jamie come up and let me hear that beautiful voice so Athens can get jealous and come up
Tribute boy
Colt of sight
I was busy man last night I missed your cold meeting it said like call to this oh my like emergency meeting
Fuck
Do I have permission to crash out?
Things are new!
No show!
Why am I not reading?
You're so psyched for now
I got to think
I got this guy you boys come when you're not busy okay you're not busy you're telling my boy
CB CB in the building
Beautiful girl
huh what up what up how many people in the building my peeps six nice it's better than
I thought I thought it was like two
with your halo then airplane mode i felt it in my skin so i was sitting like designer
and let a stranger's body keep me cool you know the spark you know the gun
you pull the string i come undone you say you love to watch me burn maybe pain's the only thing
Not to be celestial, but the way you left was biblical
So I did something ritual, cause grief for me is cynical
I might have sent a picture from a mortal bed
Just to haunt you goddamn head
I knew you crave the chaos I fed
Cause love like all they never did
Not to be divine, but I love you
Not to be celestial, but you made my dream perpetual
So I did something sexual, just to feel conceptual
I might've sent that photo from the stranger's lair
Just to prove that I still care, you'd fall apart
Cause you know it's true, no one sins the way I do
Not to be divine, but I lose
The tracks went by by, gamey.
Punch it down the block.